ati-ia.com 2019-07-19

# Privacy Policy

ATI Industrial Automation ("ATI") is committed to protecting your privacy. ATI collects and uses your personally identifiable information strictly in accordance with the provisions of the applicable laws.

This Privacy Policy tells you:

  * What Personal Information we collect
  * How we use that Personal Information
  * How we may share that Personal Information
  * How we protect that Personal Information
  * Your choices regarding your Personal Information   

By using ATI’s website (www.ati-ia.com) (collectively, the "Site") and/or submitting your Personal Information to ATI, you consent to all actions taken by us with respect to your Personal Information as stated in this Privacy Policy.

This Site contains links to other third party websites. ATI does not control and is not responsible for the operation of such websites. Please refer to the privacy policies of those websites if you have questions about their privacy practices.

ATI collects Personal Information for the purpose of providing information or updates about ATI or its products and application of to individuals who visit the Site. ATI may also use Personal Information you submit for internal purposes including the administration of the Site, data analytics, and compliance with law or legal process and ATI’s policies and procedures.

We collect Personal Information that you choose to enter into the Site. Examples of the information collected and purposes for which it is requested follow:

  * Contact Us and Request Info: You may submit an inquiry or comment to ATI along with your name, address, phone number and email address. ATI uses this information for the purpose of replying to your inquiry. 
  * Questionnaires and Surveys:  ATI may ask users of the Site to complete optional online surveys and opinion polls for the purpose of obtaining their input relating to our present or planned products and their use. These surveys help us to better meet your needs. In conducting these surveys we may ask you to provide your name and contact information so that we can provide you with information about our products. For example: by sending newsletters or other marketing material. 
  * Emails for Marketing Information:  If you give us your email address and consent to receive marketing information, ATI may send useful information about ATI products, such as advertisements, videos, e-newsletters to your email address. Please see the section in this Privacy Policy titled "Your choices regarding your Personal Information" for more information on how to opt out or unsubscribe from such emails.
  * Any Other Form of Contact Where You Voluntarily Provided Your Personal Information:  You may provide us with Personal Information in other ways including, for example, through personal contact, email, or trade show leads. ATI will handle any such Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Google Analytics   
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics tracks basic information provided by browsers, such as IP address and browser version. The information about your use of the site is transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there for a limited time period. Google will use this information on behalf of ATI to analyze your use of the site, create reports on website activity and provide additional services to ATI related to website and internet use. The IP address obtained from your browser by Google Analytics will not be combined with other Google data. You may also prevent the information regarding your use of the website (including your IP address) from being sent to or processed by Google by opting out. To do so, you must download and install the browser plugin available from the following link:  [tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) In light of the discussion on the use of analytical tools with complete IP addresses, we would like to point out, that this website uses Google Analytics with the enlargement "_anonymizeIp()" and that the IP addresses are only processed in abbreviated form to prevent them being directly linked to a particular individual.

Cookies   
ATI does not use cookies to store personal information or to provide information to third parties.

Social media    
ATI is present on various social media sites in addition to our website. Please refer to the data protection provisions of the relevant operator for the purpose and extent of the related data collection as well as the provisions for use of your data by the relevant platform.

Embedded content   
On our website, we use videos from YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA, a subsidiary of Google Inc., Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA. If you call up a web page with YouTube content, a connection to the YouTube servers is established and the content is shown on the Internet page by means of a message to your browser. This communicates to the YouTube server which of our Internet pages you have visited.

Log Files   
The Site uses Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. ATI does not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information. ATI may record the IP addresses of visitors to the Site. While an IP address may reveal your ISP or geographic area, ATI cannot determine your identity solely based upon your IP address.

Children’s Privacy   
ATI will not knowingly collect personal data from children without insisting that they seek prior parental consent if required by applicable law. We will only use or disclose personal data about a child to the extent permitted by law, to seek parental consent pursuant to local law and regulations or to protect a child. The definition of "child" or "children" should take into account applicable laws as well as national and regional cultural customs.   

ATI does not sell or lease any Personal Information such as email addresses collected on the Site. The following are some of the ways we share your information:

  * Required Disclosures:   We may be required to share Personal Information in response to a court order, subpoena, civil discovery request, other legal process, or as otherwise required by law.
  * Legal Compliance and Protections:   We may disclose account and other Personal Information when we believe disclosure is necessary to comply with the law or to protect the rights, property, or safety of ATI, our users, or others. This may include exchanging Personal Information with other companies and organizations for fraud prevention and credit risk reduction.

Remarketing   
When you visit ATI ads through Google searches, they may place cookies on your computer (or other devices you use to browse the web) that tell Google to show you additional ATI ads ("Remarketing Cookies"). Third party vendors may display ATI ads to you on sites across the Internet. You may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting  [Google's Ads Settings. ](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en) Alternatively, you may opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the  [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/) or the  [DoubleClick opt-out page.](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en#displ)   

Security measures   
ATI retains your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected and to comply with applicable laws, and your consent to such purposes(s) remains valid after termination of our relationship with you. ATI takes commercially reasonable steps to help protect and secure Personal Information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, wireless transmission or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information we collect, and your use of our Site and submission of your Personal Information is at your own risk.   

Updating Personal Information and Unsubscribing from Emails   
You may use the link in the  [“Contacting Us”](http://www.ati-ia.com/Company/SendEmail.aspx?SPID=4e412753-1185-4104-9780-7578a8d3961a) section of this policy to provide us with your updated or corrected Personal Information or to request that we delete your Personal Information. You may also choose to stop receiving marketing or promotional emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email, or by  [emailing us your request to unsubscribe.](http://www.ati-ia.com/Company/SendEmail.aspx?SPID=4e412753-1185-4104-9780-7578a8d3961a)

Data Integrity and Retention   
ATI will only process Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy and the purpose for which it was collected or authorized by you. To the extent necessary for those purposes, ATI will take reasonable steps to ensure that Personal Information is accurate, complete, current as provided, and reliable for its intended use. We may retain your Personal Information for as long as permitted or required by applicable law.

Contacting Us   
If you have any concerns about the privacy of the Personal Information you have provided to ATI, please  [email us.](http://www.ati-ia.com/Company/SendEmail.aspx?SPID=4e412753-1185-4104-9780-7578a8d3961a) ATI will investigate and attempt to resolve any complaints you have and any disputes regarding the use and disclosure of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Site or your dealings with the Site, you can email us or  [contact us](http://www.ati-ia.com/Company/SendEmail.aspx?SPID=4e412753-1185-4104-9780-7578a8d3961a) at the following address:

Webmaster   
ATI Industrial Automation   
1031 Goodworth Drive   
Apex, NC 27539 USA

Changes to this Privacy Policy    
ATI Industrial Automation reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy as needed to reflect advances in technology or new products and services. The latest version is available for viewing at all times on this website.
